

Karan Khirsariya

TECH LEAD / SENIOR DEVEOPER

PROFILE

Experienced Web-developer with demonstrated history in working with Banking and eLearning Platforms to create beautiful websites. Experience with Product based as well as Service based companies. Ready to take responsibility and ownership of the work. Currently working remotely.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth date

17 September, 1995

Nationality

Indian

Address

Rajkot, Gujarat, India

CONTACT

- karan.khirsariya@gmail.com
- +91 76210 87739
- https://karankhirsariya.dev
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/karan-khirsariya

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer

ARAB BANK (ACSS), DUBAI

DEC, 2020 - now

- Successfully created multiple **React** applications for Mortgages, Customer Onboarding, SMEs Onboarding and SMEs Lending with Localization and banking standards security.
- Created Central Backoffice application with full support of Role Based Access Control (RBAC) for different modules

Module Lead

ZEUS LEARNING PVT LTD, MUMBAI

JUN, 2020 - DEC, 2020

- Created React modules in LMS for Teachers to review and assess submissions, publish scores and check analysis dashboard.
- Created and Deployed Architecture with clients like Discovery to create Large scale Testing framework in **Python** to test eLearning website with the team of 5-6 people.

Senior Software engineer

ZEUS LEARNING PVT LTD, MUMBAI

JUN 2018 - JUN 2020

- Developed Chrome Extension to scan client's legacy Website of Interactives and automatically provide analysis for mathematical formula dependencies to minimize Project Development Speed to 2-3x.
- Created Automation Testing framework from scratch to Test MS Office Simulation Project with Java and TestNG to cover 3 lakh daily testcase executions.
- Created modules on internal LMS Project with **React** which allows students to access courses, Units and Concepts pages and submit assessments.

Software engineer

ZEUS LEARNING PVT LTD, MUMBAI

JUN 2016 - JUN 2018

• Worked with a team on Cengage project to simulate Microsoft Office Apps in Website using **HTML**, **JavaScript** and **ScriptSharp**(Script#) to teach students MS Office Applications like Word, Excel, PowerPoint with automatic step instructions.

EDUCATION

B. Tech. (Computer Engineering)

DARSHAN INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY (DARSHAN.AC.IN)

JUN 2012- JUN 2016

LANGUAGES/ LIBRARIES / FRAMEWORKS

JavaScript React CSS3 HTML Express nodeJs MUI Redux RTK Typescript

OTHER TECHNICAL CONCEPTS / SKILLS

Oauth2 SPA Localization RBAC Docker